Contact

(910) 742-1845 (Mobile) ashton111804@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ashton-avery-8044453a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Cpr Certified
Critical Thinking
Nursing

Certifications CCRN

Ashton Avery

BSN, RN CCRN

Raleigh-Durham, North Carolina Area

Summary

I am a compassionate, customer service driven RN. I started my career in Med-Surg and stayed there for 3 years. I spent a year in a medical ICU and have just started a new career in the Surgical Trauma ICU. My future goals are to expand my current knowledge of critical care nursing.

Experience

WakeMed
Critical Care RN
August 2016 - Present (3 years 11 months)
STICU

Johnston Health

RN

May 2012 - July 2016 (4 years 3 months)

smithfield, north carolina

I am a floor nurse, caring for medical-surgical inpatients as well as observation patients. I am also a charge nurse, working to coordinate assignments, increase patient satisfaction, and keep the floor running smoothly.

United Parcel Service package handler/loader June 2007 - May 2012 (5 years)

Education

North Carolina Central University

Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Nursing · (2006 - 2010)